Before they grow so big, the baobabs start out by being little.
（戸塚）バオバブだって
大きくなる前は小さいんだよ
（葉山）でも　どうしてヒツジに
バオバブを食べてほしいんだ？
But why do you want the sheep to eat the little baobabs?
そんなの　分かるでしょ？
≪（海老名）ちっがーう！→
Oh, come, come!
No!
You know what baobabs are a metaphor for, don't you?
バオバブって
何の比喩か分かるよね？
I hope you do.
分かるでしょ？→
王子様はもっとこう　上目遣いで
恥じらいながら誘うように！→
The prince needs to lean in and glance upwards, as though leading him on!
僕は　誘ってるの知りながら
意地悪するみたいに！→
Like, "You know what I want, you tease! Come, come!"
もう１回　よろしく！
はあ…
One more time, let's go!
バオバブだって　大きくなる前は
小さいんだよ？
Before they grow so big, the baobabs start out by being little.
でも　どうしてヒツジにバオバブを
食べてほしいんだ？
But why do you want the sheep to eat the little baobabs?
そんなの…　分かるでしょ？
Oh, come, come!
ふふ…　ぶはッ！
（相模）もう男子　ちゃんとやってよ
（大岡）やってるっつーの
Come on, boys, do it right!
We are!
本番　間に合うの？　ウチら
ホシミュにかけてんだからね
And you're going to finish in time?
Our class is riding on LitMus, you know!
あッ　衣装できた？
見せて　見せて～
Oh, are the costumes done?
Let me see!
へえ～　すごいね
Oh, wow!
（携帯着信）
The seams are, like, so neat!
Hey, like, would you mind, like...
（結衣）あッ
Incoming Call
Hikky
はい　どうしたの？
いきなり電話とか
Hello? What's wrong? Why the call?
（比企谷）今日　雪ノ下が
休んでるのは知ってるか？
You heard? Yukinoshita's out sick today.
[TEL]えッ？
[TEL]あいつ　体調崩したらしい
Huh?
Looks like she caught a cold.
And So, the Curtain Rises on Each's Stage,
And the Festival Grows to a Feast on Us.
♪♪～
あッ　ああ…
すっげえ
Wow.
（チャイム）
居留守か？
なら　まだいいけど
Asleep?
I hope so.
ホントに出られないくらい
体調悪かったら…
But if she's so sick she can't get up...
[ｽﾋﾟｰｶ]（雪乃）はい
ゆきのん？　私　結衣　大丈夫？
Hello?
Yukinon? It's me, Yui!
Are you okay?
[ｽﾋﾟｰｶ]ええ　大丈夫だから
Yes. I'm fine, so...
"So."
＜「だから」　だから何だ？＞
"So," what?
＜だから帰れとでも
言うつもりか？　こいつは＞
"So, go home"? Is that it?
いいから開けろ
Shut up and open the door.
[ｽﾋﾟｰｶ]どうしているの？
話がある
Why are you here?
We need to talk.
（チャイム）
どうぞ　あがって
Welcome. Come in.
おお…
そこへかけて
Have a seat.
それで　話って何かしら
What do we need to talk about?
ああ　えっと…
Um... Well...
今日ゆきのん　休んだっていうから
大丈夫かなって
You were out sick, so I was hoping you were okay.
１日休んだくらいで大げさよ
I was out for one day. You're overreacting.
すごい疲れてるんじゃないの？
まだ顔色悪いし
But you look really tired.
Like, you look kind of pale.
多少の疲れはあったけど
それくらい問題ないわ
I was somewhat tired, but not enough to be a problem.
それが問題なんじゃないの？
But that's the problem.
You don't need to take on all the work yourself.
ゆきのんが１人で
しょい込むことないじゃん
分かっているわ
だから仕事は割り振ったし
I know.
That's why I divided the tasks and reduced the load on my—
負担は軽減するように…
できてないのに？
But not enough.
私　ちょっと怒ってるからね
I'm kinda mad, okay?
I'm mad at you too, Hikky.
ヒッキーにも怒ってるから
困ってたら助けるって言ったのに
You said you'd save her if she was in trouble!
He has performed his duties as assistant historian.
記録雑務の役割は
十分に果たしていたわ
それで結構よ
でも…
That's sufficient.
But...
大丈夫　まだ時間はあるし
I'm fine.
We still have time.
家でも進めてるから
実質的な遅れはないの
I can work from home, so we're still on schedule.
由比ヶ浜さんが
心配することではないわ
You needn't be concerned, Yuigahama-san.
そんなのおかしいよ
But that's just wrong.
Is it?
そう…　かしら
誰かを頼る　皆で助け合う
Relying on others.
Helping each other out.
支え合うってのは
一般的には正しいことこの上ない
Supporting one another is the right thing to do. Nothing could be more right.
そう
でも理想論だ
I see.
But that's idealistic.
必ず誰かが貧乏くじを引く
Someone always draws the short straw.
だから人に頼れとか言う気はない
でも
So I have no intention of telling you to rely on others.
But the way you're approaching this is wrong.
お前のやり方は間違ってる
Then you know the right way to approach it?
じゃあ
正しいやり方を知っているの？
Like hell I do.
知らねえよ　だけど今までのお前の
やり方とは違ってるだろうが
But it's different from the way you've approached things thus far.
（くしゃみ）
ごめんなさい
お茶も出さずに
I'm sorry. I'll make some tea.
いいよ　そんなの
私やるし
N-No, it's fine!
I'll make it!
体調のほうは心配しないで
休んで　だいぶ楽になったから
Don't worry about my health.
I feel much better now.
As far as your health goes.
体調のほうは　か
Yukinon, um...
あのね　ゆきのん
私とヒッキーを頼って
Rely on me and Hikky.
誰かとか　皆とかじゃなくて
Not on everyone, not on others.
私達を頼って
Rely on us!
ヒッキーは…
紅茶でいいかしら
Hikky's—
Some black tea, perhaps?
ああ…
ありがとう　ゆきのん
Thanks, Yukinon.
ふう…　ふう…　ふう…
じゃあ　俺は帰るから
えッ？
Well, I'm going home.
あッ　私も
M-Me too!
はッ…
由比ヶ浜さん
Yuigahama-san.
はッ　はい
Yes?
その…　今すぐは難しいけれど
It's difficult for me now,
きっといつか　あなたを頼るわ
but one day, I will rely on you.
だから…　ありがとう
So...
Thank you.
ゆきのん
Yukinon...
でも　もう少し考えたいから
But I need time to think.
由比ヶ浜　あとよろしく
えッ？
Yuigahama, she's all yours.
Huh?
ちょ…　まッ　待って
W-Wait!
＜自分が変われば
世界が変わるというのは嘘だ＞
They say the world changes when you change, but that's not true.
You simply give in to the lies they force on you and compromise.
＜都合のいい嘘を押しつけられて
妥協させられているだけだ＞
＜本当に世界を変えるってことを
教えてやる＞
Let me show you how to really change the world.
Oh, really?
へえ～　そうなんだ
（めぐり）相模さん　皆そろったけど
Sagami-san, everyone's here.
あッ　はい
Oh, okay!
Vice-Chair
Chair
雪ノ下さん？
えッ？
Yukinoshita-san?
ああ…　それでは委員会を始めます
We will now begin the committee meeting.
本日の議題ですが　城廻会長から
連絡があったとおり
Today's topic will be, as per
Shiromeguri-senpai's suggestion,
the cultural festival slogan.
文化祭のスローガンについてです
Friendship, Effort, Victory
No, that's off.
＜それは違うだろ＞
Fun! Way too fun!
You can hear the sound of the sea breeze
Soubu High School Cultural Festival
＜そりゃダメだろう＞
That's off too.
Of One Mind
Wow. I think I know who wrote that.
＜うわあ…　書きそうなヤツに
心当たりがある＞
おッ　ああいうのちょっといいよな
１人は皆のために
Oh, I like this one!
"One for all."
俺は結構好きなんだ　ああいうの
I like these kinds of ideas.
はッ　そんなことか簡単だろ
えッ？
Yeah, looks like you get it. Simple enough.
Huh?
Force one person to be the scapegoat and eliminate them.
１人に傷を負わせて
そいつを排除する
１人は皆のために
よくやってることだろ
"One for all." You do it often?
Hikigaya...
比企谷　お前…
じゃあ最後　ウチらのほうから
We thought up this last one.
Friendship
Helping one another:
a cultural festival
うわ～
Ew.
Friendship
Helping one another:
a cultural festival
何かな　何か変だった？
Excuse me, but is there a problem?
No, not really.
いや　別に
何か言いたいことがあるのでは？
Sure you don't have a comment to make?
いや　まあ別に
No, not really.
ふ～ん　そう
イヤならほかに案出してね
Oh, good. If you do, then come up with one yourself.
それじゃあ
Then...
Man
Look closely
and one of them's slacking off:
a cultural festival
「人　よく見たら
片方　楽してる文化祭」　とか
Man. ~Look closely and one of them's slacking off: a cultural festival~.
（陽乃）あッ　はははははッ
バカだ　バカがいる
He's an idiot!
He's a total idiot!
もう最高
ああ～　ダメだ　おなか痛い
That was awesome!
Shoot, it's too much!
My sides!
（平塚）陽乃　笑いすぎだ
Haruno, stop laughing.
いやあ　私は
なかなかいいと思うけどね
No, I mean, I think it's a great idea!
うん　おもしろければＯＫ
Yeah! It's funny! All good!
比企谷　説明を
Hikigaya. Explain.
いや人という字は　人と人とが
支え合って　とか言ってますけど
Well, you know how people say the character for "man" is an ideogram of people
supporting each other?
片方　寄りかかってんじゃ
ないっすか
But one's leaning on top of the other.
誰か犠牲になることを
容認してるのが
I think the concept of "man" includes the assumption that one ends up a sacrifice.
「人」って概念だと思うんですよね
だからこの文化祭に
So I'd say it's fitting for this cultural festival and the cultural festival committee.
文化祭実行委員会に
ふさわしいんじゃないかと
犠牲というのは　具体的に何を指す
What do you mean by "sacrifice," specifically?
Look at me, I'm totally a sacrifice here.
俺とか　超犠牲でしょ
アホみたいに仕事させられてるし
I've been forced to work like a slave.
ていうか
人の仕事　押しつけられてるし
Hell, people are shoving their own work on me.
それとも
これが実行委員長　言う所の
Or maybe that's what the committee chair means by "helping one another"?
「ともに助け合う」って
ことなんですかね
助け合ったことがないんで
俺はよく知らないんですけど
I've never been helped here, so I don't know what you mean.
比企谷君
Hikigaya-kun.
却下
Rejected.
相模さん　今日は解散にしましょう
Sagami-san, let's end the meeting here.
どの道　ろくな案が出そうにないわ
えッ　でも…
We won't have any good suggestions.
Huh? But—
これで１日消費するのは
愚かな選択よ
Wasting a day on this would be a foolish decision.
実行委員全員　各自で考え
明日　決めましょう
All committee members will think of slogans and present them tomorrow.
以降の作業については
全員　全日参加にすれば
If all members work on all remaining days, we can recover the lost time.
遅れも十分取り返せる　でしょ？
Right?
Y-Yeah, right.
そう…　そうだね
じゃあ皆　明日からまた
お願いします　お疲れさまでした
Okay, everyone. We'll be meeting again tomorrow.
Thanks for coming today!
何　あれ
結局　自分が楽してーだけだろ？
What's up with him?
He just wants to slack off himself.
いいの？
何が？
Are you sure?
About what?
誤解は解いたほうが
いいと思うけれど
You might want to resolve this misunderstanding.
誤解は解けないだろう
もう解は出てるんだから
It'll never get resolved.
They're already talking about it.
そこで問題は終わってる
So the problem ends there.
どうでもいいことばかり言い訳
して　大事な時は言い訳しないのね
You make excuses for the most worthless things,
but never make excuses when it's most necessary.
There's no point in making excuses.
言い訳なんて　意味ねえよ
人間　大事な時ほど
勝手に判断するんだから
Humans make decisions themselves when it's necessary.
そうね　そうかもしれない
Yes. You might be right.
言い訳なんて無意味だもの
Excuses are meaningless.
ならもう一度
問い直すしかないわね
Perhaps I need to ask once more.
But more importantly, what was that slogan?
それより　さっきのあれは何？
センスのかけらもないわ
お前のよりはマシだ
It was absolutely tasteless.
Better than yours, at least.
何　お前　類語辞典？
What are you, a thesaurus?
あきれるくらい変わらないのね
You're disappointingly unchanging.
Humans can't change that fast.
人間そうそう変わるわけねえだろ
特にあなたは　もともと変だものね
一言多いぞ
And you were strange from the start.
If you can't say something nice...
あなたを見ていると
無理して変わろうとするのが
Sometimes, when I see you act,
I have the notion that perhaps attempting to force change would be foolish.
バカらしいことに思えてくるわ
じゃあな
ええ　さようなら
See you.
Yes. Good-bye.
また明日
また明日な
See you tomorrow.
Conference Room
Chiba's specialties! Festivals and dancing!
We're all fools, so let's dance and
This will be the slogan for this year's cultural festival.
それでは　こちらを今年の
スローガンとして決定します
Chiba's specialties! Festivals and dancing!
We're all fools, so let's dance and
相模さん　順次スローガンの
入れ込みをしたほうが
Sagami-san, we should advertise using this slogan immediately.
ああ…　うん
では入れ込みをお願いします
Oh, okay. Advertising, please.
All right, guys! Posters, on the double!
（広報Ａ）野郎ども　ポスター急ぐぞ
（広報Ｂ）副委員長
ホームページテストアップ完了です
Vice-Chair, home page test update complete!
Understood.
了解　相模さん　確認を
Sagami-san, confirm.
えッ？　ああ…　うんＯＫ
Huh? Y-Yeah, okay.
では　本番環境に移行してください
≪（広報Ｂ）了解
Upload it to the main server.
Roger!
Hey there, working hard?
（陽乃）やあやあ
しっかり働いているかね？
ご覧のとおりですよ
As you can see.
しっかりとは
働いてないみたいだね
Doesn't look like you're working that hard.
Historian
＜何でだよ　超やってんだろ＞
Why!? I totally am!
I mean, you haven't put your own achievements in the record.
だってさ　この議事録には
比企谷君の功績が
入っていないじゃない
Time for a quiz!
ここでクイズです　集団を最も
団結させる存在は何でしょう？
What makes a group come together like nothing other?
冷酷な指導者ですか？
A coldhearted tyrant?
またまた～　知ってるくせに
Oh, come on. You know.
敵の存在だよ
It's an enemy.
Well, the enemy here was kinda wimpy.
まッ　敵がちょ～っと小物だけどね
ほっとけ
Oh, shut up.
でも　君みたいな悪者が　ちゃんと
やってるなら対抗心が出るでしょ
But as long as you played the villain, you got a heroic response.
敵がしっかりしてないと
成長もしないからね
If the enemy slacks off, the group doesn't grow.
争いこそが
技術を発展させるのであ～る
Conflict brings about the development of technology.
Wow, could you shut up?
＜うわッ　うぜえ＞
Um...
あの　もしかしてわざと雪ノ下に…
Did you purposely make—
I don't like boys who can catch on.
お姉さん　勘のいいガキは嫌いよ
雑務　仕事をしなさい
Assistant, back to work.
スローガン決定に伴う書類の制作
それから議事録
Document that the slogan has been determined.
Also, the record of proceedings.
各団体へのスローガンの通達メール
送っておいて
Inform all participants of the slogan as well.
それと　ついでに企画申請書類を
取り込んでサーバーにアップも
Oh, and upload all group participation requests to the server as well.
とにかく　今日中によろしく
私もやろうか？
Finish it all today.
Need me to help too?
姉さんは邪魔だから帰って
You just get in the way. Go home.
How mean!
ひどい　雪乃ちゃんひどい
Yukino-chan, you're so mean!
まあ　暇だし
勝手にやっちゃうんだけどね
Well, I'm bored, so I'll help out anyway.
はあ…　予算の見直しをするから
勝手にやるなら　そっちにして
We need to review the finances again. Could you do that?
Okay!
はーい！　やっぱ文実は
こうでなきゃ→
Now this is how you get work done!
ああ～　今すっごく充実してるな
I'm feeling so fulfilled right now!
開演３分前　開演３分前
Three minutes to curtains. Three minutes to curtains.
[TEL]雪ノ下です　各員に通達
Yukinoshita to all hands.
[TEL]オンタイムで進行します
問題があれば即時発報を
We are proceeding on time.
Report any delays immediately.
[TEL]（照明）照明　問題なし
[TEL]（ＰＡ）こちらＰＡ　問題ないです
Lights, all clear!
PA system, all clear!
[TEL]（楽屋裏）キャストさん
準備やや押しです→
Green room, cast preparations behind, but should complete before show time.
[TEL]けど　出番までには
間に合いそうです
All hands, stand by for cue.
了解　ではキュー出しまで
各自　待機
[TEL]１０秒前　８　７　６　５　４
Ten seconds.
Eight.
Seven.
Six.
Five.
Four.
Soubu High School Cultural Festival
Chiba's specialties! Festivals and dancing!
We're all fools, so let's dance and
[TEL]３　２　１
Three.
Two.
One.
Soubu High School Cultural Festival
Chiba's specialties! Festivals and dancing!
We're all fools, so let's dance and
Are you ready to culture?!
お前ら　文化してるか～！
（歓声）
Chiba's specialties! Festivals and...
千葉の名物　踊りと
（観客）祭り～
...dancing!
We're all fools, so let's dance and...
同じ阿呆なら　踊らにゃ
（観客）Ｓｉｎｇ　ａ　Ｓｏｎｇ！
...sing a song!
♪♪～
[TEL]（ＰＡ）こちらＰＡ
間もなく曲あけます
PA here. Cutting music momentarily.
了解　相模委員長　スタンバイします
Roger. Chairwoman Sagami, stand by.
では続いて　文化祭実行委員長より
ごあいさつです
And now, a word from the committee chairwoman!
みッ…
Hi—
（ハウリングして観客が笑う）
では気を取り直して
実行委員長　どうぞ
Okay, let's have a do-over!
Committee chairwoman, go ahead!
時間　押してんな
We're falling behind schedule.
Hang in there!
[TEL]比企谷君
巻くように指示を出して
Hikigaya-kun, signal her to wrap it up.
さっきから出してる
見えてないみたいだけど
I've been signalling.
She can't see it.
[TEL]そう…　私の人選ミスかしら
I see. Perhaps I chose the wrong position for you.
それは俺の存在感のなさを
揶揄しているのか
Is that a jab at my inability to stand out?
あら　そんなこと言ってないわ
それよりどこにいるの　客席？
I never said that.
More importantly, where are you?
In the audience?
[TEL]めっちゃ揶揄してんじゃねえか
ていうか　見えてんだろ　お前
Hell, that's a freaking hook!
You can totally see me!
I am the cultural festival committee chair, Sagami Minami.
Um... Vice-Chair, all hands are online.
[TEL]（委員Ａ）あの　副委員長
皆に聞こえてます
≪（相模）今年のスローガンは
千葉の名物…
This year's slogan is Chiba's specialties: festivals and dancing.
[TEL]以降のスケジュールを繰り上げます
各自　そのつもりで
We're proceeding according to schedule. All hands, prepare.
We're all fools, so let's dance and sing a song.
Chiba's specialties!
Festivals and dancing!
We're all fools,
so let's dance
Cultural
Festival
Soubu
High School
The Little Prince
≪（戸塚）僕は
何も分かってなかったんだ
The Little Prince
I did not know how to understand anything!
言葉に　だまされるべきじゃ
なかった
I ought not to have listened to him.
He cast his fragrance and radiance over me.
彼は　いい匂いがしたし
いつも輝いていた
You were too young to know how to love him.
仕方ないよ　君はまだ若い
彼の愛し方を知らなかったんだ
＜何この役　もしかして
俺が出るべきだった？＞
What's up with that role?
She wanted me to play it?
今晩　君はきちゃいけない
そんな　どうして？→
Tonight—you know... do not come.
No, but why not?
I said, I shall not leave you.
俺達は
ずっと一緒だって言ったろ
＜おかしい　原作のセリフすら
全部ＢＬに聞こえる＞
Something's wrong here.
The lines from the book sound like slash fiction now.
僕を見ると　悲しむかもしれない
It was wrong of you to come. You will suffer.
俺達はずっと一緒だ
I shall not leave you!
仕方がないんだ
僕のことは諦めて
Here it is! Let me go on by myself!
俺達は　ずっと一緒なんだ！
I shall not leave you!
Blugha!
ぶは～ッ
＜ダメだ　こいつ
早くなんとかしないと＞
She's done for.
Better do something quick.
君は　俺よりも彼を選んだんだな→
So you have chosen him over me.
But it is well.
でもいいんだ　すぐに会えるから
I shall see you again soon.
だって　俺の描いたヒツジの口輪は
壊れているからね
Because...
When I drew the muzzle for the sheep,
I did not draw the leather strap.
（拍手）
ふふ…　ヒツジ…
Heh-heh. Sheep.
On Break
Reception
お疲れ　どうだった？
Nice work.
How was it?
よかったんじゃねえのか？
お客さんも喜んでたし
Good, I'm guessing.
The customers enjoyed it.
On Break
Reception
皆　ずっと頑張ってたからね
Everyone worked really hard on it.
まあ　そうな
頑張ってたんじゃないか
Yeah, I guess they all did.
いなかったから　よく知らんが
I wasn't around, so I don't know.
The committee was crazy busy, so you couldn't really help, huh?
文実あったし　クラスのほう
出れてないから仕方ないよ
Hey, what the hell?
（もめている男子生徒）
You're breaking my balls, man!
Let us in already!
What's wrong with you?
How long you gonna keep us waiting?!
うわ～　大変そうだね
That doesn't look good.
あのままだと収拾つかなく
なるんじゃねえのか
It's going to get out of hand at this rate.
（笛）
All right, everyone. Let's roll.
皆　よろしく
（役員Ａ）こちらに並んでください
（役員Ｂ）最後尾　こちらになります
Please form two lines here.
Back of Line
The back of the line is over here!
Ｅ組　代表者はいるかしら？
Is the 2-E representative here?
Yukinon's so cool.
ゆきのん　カッコイイな
ちょっと元気になったよね
She's looking a lot better now.
そうだな
Guess so.
なあ　ちょっと聞いていいか？
はッ　何？
Hey, mind if I ask something?
Huh? What?
雪ノ下の家に行った時
何か話したのか？
Did you talk about anything when you were at Yukinoshita's place?
なーんにも
はッ？
Not a thing.
ヒッキーが帰ってからは　おなかすいた
から　一緒にご飯食べて
After you went home, we were hungry, so we ate dinner together,
何かＤＶＤ見て　で私は帰った
we watched some TV,
and I went home.
だから　ヒッキーが知りたいことは
何も聞いてないよ
So she didn't tell me anything you want to know about.
Reception
いや　別に知りたいこととかねえよ
Hey, there isn't anything I want to know about.
Reception
そう？　私は知りたかったけどね
Really?
Reception
I wanted to know.
私ね　ゆきのんのことは
待つことにしたの
Reception
I've decided to wait for Yukinon.
ゆきのんはたぶん　話そう
近づこうってしてるから
I think Yukinon's trying her best to approach us and talk about it.
だから待つの
So I'll wait.
でも　待ってても
どうしようもない人は待たない
But I won't wait for someone who won't try even if you wait.
うん？　まあ　どうしようもない
ヤツ待っても仕方ない…
Huh?
Well, if they aren't trying, there's no point waiting—
違うよ
No.
待たないで　こっちからいくの
I won't wait and do it myself.
おお…
そうか
うん　そうだ
Oh, really?
Yeah. Really.
あッ　忘れてた
お昼まだでしょ？
Oh, right!
You haven't had lunch, right?
ほら　ハニトー
Here! Honey toast!
Wow.
おお…
そんな珍しい物でもないでしょう
It's not that rare, is it?
＜うん？
てか　これパンだろ　マジで＞
Hm?
Hold on, this is actually bread.
＜もうちょっとパン感を消す
努力しなかったのかよ＞
Shouldn't you try to make it look not like bread?
＜パン丸出しだぞ　超パン＞
It's all bread here.
Totally bread.
On Break
うんま～
Yum!
The bread's hard.
＜パン堅え　中のほうまで
ハチミツが染みてねえ＞
The honey hasn't soaked into it.
＜これ途中からモサモサ…
罰ゲームだな＞
And it's all chewy.
What'd I do to deserve this?
生クリーム　うまッ！
Whipped cream's so yummy!
＜それハニトーである必要
あったのかよ＞
Then did it have to be honey toast?
＜しかも　その生クリーム
俺のから奪ってるだろ　お前＞
And you took that cream from my half!
Well, I guess it's good.
＜うん…　まあ　うまい…　かな＞
ああ～　おなかいっぱい
I'm so full!
そういや　いくらだった？
いいって別に　これくらい
Reception
Oh, right. How much was it?
It's okay, it wasn't much!
いや　そういう訳にもいかんだろ
いいってば
Hey, it doesn't work like that.
I said, it's fine.
俺は養われる気はあるが
施しを受ける気はない
While I enjoy the idea of being supported,
I have no intention of accepting charity.
何　そのよく分かんないプライド
What's with that messed up policy?
分かった　じゃあ今度ハニトー
おごってもらうことにする　パセラで
Fine. You're taking me out for honey toast sometime.
At Pasela.
You're choosing the place?
場所　指定すんのかよ
＜てことは…　さ…＞
Does that mean... uh...
Oh.
あッ
何か　別のもんでもいいか？
うん　いいよ　で　いつにする？
Hey, can I treat you to something else instead?
Yeah, sure!
When are we doing it?
ああ　あの…　すいません
ちょっとよく考えさせてください
Uh...
Sorry.
Could you give me time to think?
Reception
mitsumeru tabi doki doki shiteru
Each time I see you, my heart beats faster
♪♪～
kimi ni motto chikadzukitai yo
I want to get closer to you
amai yokan tokechau mae ni
Before the sweet dream melts away
kidzuite ne tokubetsu ni naritai
Notice my feelings, I want to be special to you
Next time:
And So, His and Her and Her Youths
Continue Being Wrong.
And So, His and Her and Her Youths Continue Being Wrong.
＜次回＞